# MAKSYMILIAN PIERCHAŁA

Polna 89, 44-178 Przyszowice, 794011222

#### pierchala.maks@gmail.com

I am a web development passionate, looking for first professional experience in this area, preferably as a Junior Developer. I stand out as an out-box thinker and a creative person. I gladly increase my qualifications, as an 19-year-old self-taught developer, who cares about commissioned work.

## **EXPERIENCE**

07.2019 - 09.2019

#### WAREHOUSEMAN, NAGEL POLAND

Keeping track of orders, completing and submitting them for send out, verifying the number and the quality of deliveries. Mainly working as a team.

04.2022 - 08.2022

#### WAREHOUSEMAN, DECATHLON

Picking up products to complete orders, addressing delivered packages and keeping track of the number of products. Mainly working as a team.

11.2022 - CURRENTLY

#### PIZZA DELIVERY MAN, NOCNY MAREK

Delivering orders to clients, working as a team, making pizza.

### **EDUCATION**

2019 - 2023

# CLASS WITH EXTENDED MATHS AND PHYSICS, IV LICEUM OGÓLNOKSZTAŁCĄCE W GLIWICACH

Double scholarship holder

2023

# POLITECHNIKA ŚLĄSKA W GLIWICACH, INFORMATICS

#### **SKILLS**

- Java, Javascript, Typescript,
- React, NextJs, Nodejs, Expressjs
- Postman, Spring Boot, Postgresql
- SQL, MongoDB/mongoose

- Git, GitHub
- Basic knowledge of Linux
- Ability to speak English at C1 level.

#### **HOBBIES**

Gym, swimming, maths and programming

GITHUB: https://github.com/MaxamatO

PORTFOLIO: https://maxamato.github.io/Portfolio

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European

Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).